[咒语]
该死的巫师
Freaking witches.
我知道怎么关闭地狱之门了
I figured out how to close the gates of hell.
上帝建立了一系列测试  等你都完成了
God built a series of tests, and when you've done all three,
就可以去关门了
you can slam the gates.
好吧  第一项是什么
All right. Where do we start?
你得杀一只地狱之犬并浸于它的血中
You've got to kill a hound of hell and bathe in its blood.
我要你安安全全的
I need you to be safe.
所以我要去做这些测试
So I'm gonna do these trials.
萨姆  我没能通过测试
Sam, I didn't pass the test.
但是我通过了  剩下的都让我来
But I did, and I'm doing the rest of them.
想得美
My ass you are!
我能行
I can do this.
如今
密苏里州  圣路易斯
刚刚真不赖
That was great,
我想给你点东西
and I want to give you a little something.
拿着  谢谢
Here you go. Thanks.
-谢谢你  -嗯
- Thank you. - Yeah.
看来我今晚不走运啊
Guess it's not my night.
看来是的
Guess not.
凶鬼恶灵
第八季 第十五集
男人最好的炮友
你说过的所有的傻话
You know, of all the lame-ass things you've ever said,
这绝对是最傻的
that's got to be the lame-assiest.
抱歉  但我就是觉得
I'm sorry, but I happen to think
夏普比科里更搞笑
Shemp was a funnier stooge than Curly.
《三个臭皮匠》[美国20世纪早期到中期的一部杂耍和喜剧]的演员
科里是个天才啊
Curly was a freaking genius!
我总觉得科里的笑点太明显了
I always found Curly's work a bit obvious.
本来就是要明显啊  他们是臭皮匠
It's supposed to be obvious, man. They're stooges.
我们今晚给詹姆斯打电话吗
So, we calling James tonight?
明天再打吧
No. I'll just call him tomorrow.
这一路真辛苦
That drive was a bitch.
不知道他什么事
I wonder what he wanted.
他短信里说需要我们帮忙
Well, his text said that he needed help.
他是个警察  应该是跟工作有关
He's a cop. I figured it was work-related.
我们的确欠他一个人情
Yeah, well, we do owe him.
他救过我们一次  萨姆
The guy saved our lives once, Sammy.
-他又不是...  -救过我们吗
- I mean, it's not like the guy - - Saved our lives?
我去买啤酒  你要什么吗
I'm gonna go for a beer run. You need anything?
不用
No, I'm good.
你确定
You sure?
嗯
Yeah.
因为你刚刚宰了一头地狱之犬
'cause you did just gank a hellhound,
可不是件小事
which is no slice of pie,
还不知道后面有什么事呢
and, uh, there is a mine field of who knows what crap ahead.
我只是想确保你真的没事
Just want to make sure that you are okay.
我没事
I'm good.
我们可以再找一条地狱之犬来
'cause, you know, we could find another devil dog.
你别插手
You could tag out.
我去宰了他
I could snuff the son of a bitch.
迪恩  凯文都不知道下一项测试是什么
Dean, Kevin doesn't even know what the next trial is yet.
不管你在担心什么  别担心了
So whatever it is you're worried about, stop.
我会准备好的
I'll be ready.
你乖吗
Hey. You friendly?
真乖  好吧
Friendly. Good. All right.
你可真漂亮
You're a pretty dog.
是嘛
Oh, really?
要我挠挠你的肚皮吗
You want, uh -- you want a little belly scratch, huh?
你是谁家的
So, who do you belong to?
好吧  没有狗牌
Right. No tags.
你为什么跑到这儿来了
Uh, what are you doing here?
不好
Oh, no.
好吧
Okay, okay, okay.
你先别发火
Before you get pissed off, look,
我得告诉你这不是我的错
I-I just want you to know this isn't my fault.
她自己跑来挠门的
She just showed up at the door, okay?
也没踩泥巴进来  只是想让我挠挠她肚子
Didn't track in any mud. Just wanted her belly scratched.
我觉得或许可以留她一晚
I-I figured maybe she could stay tonight,
明天给她找个家
and we'd try and find her a home tomorrow.
她可以留一晚
She can stay the night.
两秒之前她还是条狗
Two seconds ago, she was a dog.
好吧  你是什么东西
All right, who the hell are you?
不是变形怪  把刀收起来吧
Not a shapeshifter, so you can stash the blade.
我是灵兽
I'm a familiar.
什么
A what?
巫师的伴侣  有些巫师有
Companion to a witch -- some witches.
在人和动物之间来回变身
Split their time between human and animal form.
我另一种形态时能更准确地判断一个人
I get a more accurate read on people in my other persona.
这样在汽车酒店接近一个人
Approaching guys in a motel room like this --
可能会变得很复杂
well, it gets complicated.
我叫波西亚  我是詹姆斯・弗兰普顿的灵兽
My name's Portia. I belong to James Frampton.
不不
No. No, no.
这可不对
See, that -- that doesn't work for us,
那么说的话  詹姆斯不就是巫师了吗
'cause that would mean that our buddy James is a witch.
你真灵光啊
Wow. You're quick.
詹姆斯是巫师吗
James is a freaking witch?
你们相遇的时候他不是
He wasn't when you met him,
但你们上次跟他合作的案子
but that last case you worked on with him --
疯狂的炼金术士  相当麻烦
Uh, lunatic alchemist. It was nasty.
詹姆斯想近一步了解那些东西
James wanted to learn more about that world --
妖术  魔法
The black arts, witchcraft.
变成了他生活的重心
It became the center of his life.
等等  你是说
Wait, so you're telling me
詹姆斯因为我们从警察变成了巫师吗
that James the cop became a witch because of us?
你不是爱狗之人  是吧
You don't like dogs, do you?
等等  詹姆斯不做警察了吗
Wait. So James isn't a cop anymore?
当然做
Sure he is.
凶案组警探
Homicide detective.
他的法力让他查案更厉害了
His new powers make his work even better.
那他找我们什么事
Then what does he need from us?
他出了点事
Well, something's been happening to him.
起先是头疼欲裂
It started with excruciating headaches,
耳际有尖叫声  可怕的噩梦
screaming sounds in his ears, horrible nightmares.
不能睡觉也不能思考  他无法工作
Unable to sleep or think. He can't work.
就像是精神崩溃
It -- it's like he's having a breakdown.
或许你们能帮他
Maybe you can find a way to help him.
问题是
Well, here's the thing.
我不怎么喜欢巫师
Uh, witches -- not real fans.
是吗
Really?
詹姆斯是个功勋卓著的警察
Well, James is a cop with a spotless record.
他只用法力做好事
He's used his skills for nothing but good.
所以你能不能暂时放下
So why don't you lose the ignorant bigotry
你无知的偏见  给他个机会
for maybe two seconds and give him a shot?
真性感啊
That was incredibly hot.
这话我不否认
It was pretty hot.
你还是悠着点吧
You might want to go easy on that.
天呐  你气色好差
God, you look awful.
还没好转吗
Not getting any better?
更糟了
Worse.
我不知道我是怎么了
I don't know what's happening to me.
这些噩梦  就像
These dreams they're like, um --
是折磨
like torture.
你没说噩梦的事
You didn't mention dreams.
黑暗  血腥
Dark, bloody.
斯宾塞  这些噩梦
Spencer, they, uh --
真要吓死我了
they scare the hell out of me.
感觉那么真实
They're so real.
夜复一夜
Just night after night.
够了  詹姆斯
Enough, James.
你得去找人帮你
It's time to see someone.
谁
Who?
能去找谁
Who do we see?
这东西又没得治
There's no medicine for this.
或许你只是需要歇歇
Maybe you just need time away.
那可不够
It's way beyond that.
詹姆斯  你承受不住了
James, it's too much --
你做了那么多
all that you've taken on.
不只是干得多的问题  还有工作本身
Not just the workload, but the nature of the work.
你看看周围
Look around.
这儿还有第二个警察吗
See a lot of cops, do you?
这样的生活是边缘的生活
Life in this realm is life on the fringe.
我们不于周围融合
We don't fit.
你要怎么调解你自身和你的工作
How do you reconcile what you are with what you do?
我不知道波西亚去哪了
I don't know where Portia is.
什么
What?
她走了
She's gone.
我觉得我把她推开了
I think I'm pushing her away.
詹姆斯做的梦
So, these dreams James is having --
他觉得都是真的
he thinks that they're real?
他觉得他是真杀人了吗
He thinks that he is actually killing people?
是的
I think so.
至少他开始屏蔽我之前  我听到了这些
At least that's what I picked up before he started blocking me.
什么叫屏蔽
What does that mean, blocking you?
灵兽和主人
Familiars and their masters --
有心灵感应
we can communicate telepathically.
我可以随时进入詹姆斯的脑袋
I can get inside of James' head anytime I want.
但他屏蔽了我
But he shut me out.
那你是觉得他脑海里有他不想
So, what, you think maybe there's something in there
你看到的东西吗
he doesn't want you to see?
有可能吧
Possibly, yeah --
可能是某种黑暗的  对他不利的东西
Something dark, you know, that's destroying him.
他不能去报警  又不信任其他巫师
He can't go to the police, and he doesn't trust other witches.
但他信任我们
But he trusts us?
你知道我们是谁吧
You do know who we are, right?
我们是詹姆斯这种人最不该
We're the last people that somebody like James
倾诉的对象
needs to be telling his troubles to.
是我的主意
This was my idea.
是我以詹姆斯的名义发了短信
I was the one who sent you the text under James' name.
他不知道你们来了
He doesn't know you're here.
但  我觉得你们可能是他唯一的希望了
But...I think you're maybe all he has.
有人吗
Someone there?
你无权这么做
You've no right to do this.
我担心你
I was afraid for your life!
我怎么样与他们无关
My life is none of their business!
萨姆  迪恩
Sam, Dean.
居然搞上巫术了  詹姆斯
Witchcraft, James? Really?
你是怎么想的啊
What the hell are you thinking?
你是来帮我还是骂我的
You come to help or pile on?
我只是想说  掺和那东西
I'm just saying, you screw with that stuff,
你会发疯的
you're gonna fry your wiring.
行了
All right.
跟我们说说这些梦吧
Look, why don't you tell us about these dreams?
她说梦里有人丧命
She said people were dying in them.
丧命
"Dying"?
是被撕碎
They were torn to bits.
我能感觉到自己的手抓裂他们的肉
I, uh, I could feel my fingers ripping into their flesh.
但的确是梦吗
But they were dreams?
我醒来时在床上
Well, I, uh, woke up in my bed.
那就是梦了
Okay, so...dreams?
我不确定
I'm not so sure.
这些都没用  詹姆斯
Not helping, James.
这些人  他们死了
Those people -- they died.
我跟分局核实过
I checked with the precinct.
好吧  或许你是听说了这些事
All right, well, maybe you heard it,
就记在了心里
and it stuck in your head.
你以为我自己没这么想过吗
You're -- you don't think I-I told myself all that?
你以为我没对自己说  "那不是我
You don't think I didn't say, "That wasn't me.
我不会做那种事"吗
I couldn't have done such a thing"?
那是你的吗
Is it yours?
詹姆斯・马丁・弗兰普顿
James Martin Frampton.
我是怎么了
What's happening to me?
会不会是这样
Well, how about this?
你惹怒了其他巫师
Um, you pissed off another witch,
他或她给你下了咒  逼你...
and he or she hexed you and forced you to...
有这可能  但我没听过这种事
It's possible, I suppose, but I never heard of it.
你做过多少这样的梦了
How many of these dreams have you had?
四次
Four.
最后一次是昨晚
The most recent one is last night.
我袭击了一个盲人
Uh, it was a blind man.
我
I, uh...
我掐着他
I was choking him, and, uh...
好吧  詹姆斯
All right, James, we're gonna --
我们会帮你想办法
we're gonna help you figure this out,
但你自己也得做你该做的
but you're gonna have to do your part.
做什么
Which is?
你得留在这儿
You're gonna have to stay put.
软禁在这儿
House arrest, my friend.
最后一个了
Got the last of it.
好啊  我在看犯罪现场的报告
All right. Well, I have been looking at the crime-scene reports,
都跟詹姆斯跟我们说的一样
and they are exactly the same as James told us --
被害人  日期和地点
Vics, dates, location.
最后一个是个盲人  跟他说的一样
The most recent one was a blind man, just like he said.
这可不好
That's not good.
我还查了他警队的记录
Also, I looked into his record on the force.
他差不多是一夜从菜鸟警探变成了副队
He went from rookie detective to lieutenant basically overnight,
而且过去四年
and in the last four years,
他的破案率是百分之百
his solve rate's been right at about 100%.
当然了
Of course.
他有"神助"嘛
He's got the booga-booga on his side.
我们从没真正见过
Man, you know that we've never actually seen
鲍比这个杀巫师的咒语施效吧
this witch-killing spell of Bobby's work, right?
这东西说不准啊
I mean, this is not a sure thing.
什么事说得准过
Is anything we ever do a sure thing?
没有  但我只是希望
Well, no, but I would just like to
尽可能有点胜算
have the odds in our favor as much as possible.
好吧
Right.
我很担心
Well, I'm concerned.
担心  杀巫师咒
Concerned about the, uh -- the witch-killing spell...
还是我会搞砸这几项测试
...or that I'm gonna mess these trials up?
如果我们继续做下去
Look, we get too far down the road with this,
就不能回头了
we can't go back,
我想替你也晚了
and it'll be too late for me to jump in.
谁说就一定会那样
Who says that you're gonna have to?
说不定我这次真能做到呢
You know, maybe I'll actually pull this one off.
我只是说说
I'm just saying.
我知道你想说什么  迪恩  你说过了
I know what you're saying, Dean. You've said it.
我一直反复地想
You know, I've been going over this and over this,
问自己你为什么就不信任我
asking myself "Why doesn't he trust me?"
最终我终于想通了
And it occurred to me, finally.
你不是不信任我
It's not that you don't trust me.
而是你只信任自己
It's that you can only trust you.
你说完了吗
Are you done?
你说完了我就不说了
Yeah, I'm done if you're done.
等我把咒语准备好了
You know, once I get this put together,
就不能犹豫了
we can't hesitate.
需要用的时候  就得用
If we got to use it, we use it.
你是指我们找到害詹姆斯的那个巫师时吗
You mean if we find the witch that's doing this to James?
或者如果就是他本人
Or if there is no other witch.
或者  我们不是第一次放走人了  迪恩
Or it wouldn't be the first free pass we've given, Dean.
听着  我也喜欢詹姆斯
Look, I like James as much as the next guy,
但是现在在死人呢
but people are getting ganked here.
而且  本尼  凯特
Besides, Benny, Kate --
他们的命运不是自己选的
they were forced to be what they are.
而詹姆斯是自己选了这条路
James chose this.
被害人都死得很惨
Vics were all torn up pretty bad.
就像有人赤手撕碎了他们
Like someone shredded them with their bare hands.
这怎么可能呢  艾德
Like that could happen. Ed?
艾德・斯托尔兹  他在查这个案子
Ed Stoltz. He's lead on the case.
这是基思特工
Special agent Keith.
乔什说你们的线索不多
Josh here tells me you don't have a lot to go on.
是啊  作案地点分散
Yeah. Isolated parts of the city,
被害人都没什么亲友
vics who meant nothing to nobody, so...
这样啊
Right.
我和我的搭档看过了犯罪现场
Well, uh, my partner and I had a look at the crime scenes.
局里的脚步还真慢
Things really must be slow at the bureau.
现场我们都查过了
Locations have already been knocked down.
但是我们找到了这块织物
Well, we did manage to find this piece of fabric.
有遗漏也是难免的
Things get overlooked. It happens.
你查下血好吗
Why don't you run the blood?
可能是被害人或者凶手
It could be the vic. It could be the doers.
看看能不能找到匹配
Let's see if we get a match.
确实有个目击者称见到一个
A witness did mention seeing a man in a suit
穿白衬衫和西装的人离开现场
and a white shirt leaving the area, so --
你在报告中没提及目击者
You didn't mention a witness in your report.
还有别的吗
Anything else?
没了
No.
回头告诉你分析结果
We'll get back to you on the lab work.
-如果没别的事  -这个目击者
- So if that's all - - Sure, but this witness --
他没说别的了  基思特工
That's all that was said, agent Keith.
我们线索真的不多
We really don't have a lot here, okay?
再联系
We'll be in touch.
他们都是在瞪我吗
Am I getting the stink eye in here or what?
他们看得出你是外人
They can tell you're an outsider.
这都是巫师
Are they all witches?
还有别的
And stuff.
但如果有什么跟詹姆斯相关的消息
But if there's information out here about James,
他们肯定知道
they'll know.
詹姆斯怎么找到你的
How did James find you, anyway?
不是那样的
Not the way it works.
是灵兽找到主人  然后与他形影不离
The familiar finds the master, and they become inseparable.
很多人对宠物也是这样
Guess a lot of people feel that way about their pets.
怎么了
What?
我不是詹姆斯的宠物
I'm not James' pet.
并不总是
Well, not all the time.
从来不是
Not ever.
主人和灵兽之间
The master and the familiar --
有着牢不可破的联系  就像灵魂的融合
there's an unbreakable bond, like a melding of souls.
我们愿意为对方献出生命
We would die for each other.
波西亚
Portia.
过来
Over here.
迪恩  这位是菲利普・勒沙
Dean, Meet Phillippe LeChat.
迪恩是底特律来的巫士
Dean's a wiccan from Detroit.
是吗
Really?
请坐
Well...sit, sit.
斯宾塞在吗
Spencer here?
就在哪吧
Somewhere.
真奇怪  周围有猫我才这样
That's weird. That only happens around cats.
跟我说说詹姆斯
Tell me about James.
外面很多传言
Lot of buzz out there.
都是流言蜚语
All gossip.
群落对他好像不太友好
The community has a little attitude going.
他活该
He brings it on himself.
当警察  巫师警察  他疯了吧
The whole cop thing -- witch cop -- is he nuts?
我也这么说
I said the exact same thing.
还有你  宝贝
Then there's you, babe.
这事没完  波西亚  你心里清楚
It isn't done, Portia, and you know it.
抱歉  提点一下我  什么没完
I'm sorry. Uh, remind me, what -- what isn't done?
波西亚
Portia.
我是个巫士
Uh, I'm a -- I'm a wiccan.
来自底特律
I'm from Detroit.
问斯宾塞吧
Spencer's the man to ask.
好的
Oh, okay.
你知道有没有咒语
Uh... you ever heard of a-a spell
可以让一个巫师控制其他巫师
where a witch can control the actions of another witch?
没有  从没听说过
No, I never heard of a thing like that.
这不可能吧
I don't think it's possible.
詹姆斯怎么样了
How's James?
好多了  我会转达你的关心
Better. I'll tell him you asked.
菲利普  该走了
Philippe, it's time we were going.
好的
Of course.
晚安
Good night.
很高兴见到你
So nice to meet you.
我就知道
I knew it.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
喂
Yeah.
你在哪
Where are you?
巫师酒吧  怎么了
Some witch bar. Why?
詹姆斯衬衫上的血液检测报告出来了
Listen, I just got the lab work back from the blood on James' shirt.
-怎么样  -不妙
- And? - Not good.
和三号死者的血液匹配
Blood's an exact match to victim number three.
那结果不言自明了吧
Well, that pretty much says it all, doesn't it?
是的
Yeah.
我真不想这么做
I hate doing this to you.
没事的  真的
It's okay. Really.
我们不必这样做
We don't have to.
他们不会知道的
You know, they won't find out.
波西亚
Portia...
我要是相信自己的清白
If I believe I'm innocent,
就得做正确的事
I have to do the right thing.
要是我有罪  就更得做正确的事
And if I'm not innocent, I have to do the right thing.
告诉我  总有一天这事会结束
Tell me one day this will be over.
我爱你
I love you.
不
No!
不  迪恩
No, Dean!
你们一定要听我说  不是詹姆斯干的
You have to listen to me, please. It's not James.
今晚  我和詹姆斯很亲近
Tonight, James and I were close,
没有隔阂  十分亲密
without psychological walls -- intimate.
我不...
I don't --
他们做爱了
They had sex.
这...我还真没想到
I, uh -- I didn't expect that.
我们的关系与众不同
We have an unusual relationship.
灵兽不该和巫师上床的
Familiars aren't supposed to be sexually involved with their witches.
这也可以理解  鉴于你是个...
Understandable, you know, considering that you're a...
而他是个...
Well, and that he's...
真是...
That's --
帮个忙吧
Little help here?
不帮
No?
我和詹姆斯已经好几周没做爱了
James and I -- we hadn't made love in weeks.
他被痛苦吞没  将我关在了心门之外
His agony ate him up, and he shut me out.
可是今晚  我看到了他的思想
But tonight, I saw his thoughts --
对于凶杀的回忆
Memories of the murders.
抱歉  你是要劝我们放过詹姆斯...
I'm sorry, is this you trying to talk us out of ganking James or --
迪恩  我看到的只有杀戮
Dean, that's all I saw -- just the kills.
没有准备  没有思想过程
No preparation, no thought process,
没有预谋  没有动机
no anticipation, no motive.
只有毫无前因后果的杀戮
Just the kills without context.
对凶案没有其它意识吗
No other awareness of the crimes?
没有
No.
这是不是至少说明了他是被人控制的
Doesn't that at least suggest he's under another's control?
斯宾塞说那不可能
Spencer said that wasn't possible.
他说他从没听说过
He said he'd never heard of it.
詹姆斯已经被锁起来了
James is chained.
被制服了
He's confined.
至少试一试吧
At least take a shot.
先生们
Gentlemen.
还在调查这个小案子
Still investigating this crappy little case?
没想到联调局竟然这么闲
I'm awed the bureau has so much time on its hands.
我们在选择案件上可以自行做主
Right. Well, we have some, uh, individual discretion to pursue cases.
詹姆斯・弗兰普顿
回头找你  艾德
I'll catch up later, Ed.
是啊  但是时间久了就会变成悬案
Yeah, but at some point, cases like this go cold,
我相信你也知道
as I'm sure you're aware.
就是没法查下去了
Just not enough to keep them floating -- that's all.
当然  没有新线索
Sure. No new leads, then?
没有  案子就要被搁置了
No. And it's drifting towards the back burner, really.
我们没这么多人手
We just don't have the manpower.
那失去弗兰普顿副队这样的人才
Then it must have been tough to lose a valuable resource
一定是雪上加霜
like Lieutenant Frampton.
是这样  我和他...我们...
See, he and I -- we, uh --
我们从前一起办过案
We caught a case together a while back.
我没有失去他
Well, he's not lost to me.
他在休假
He's -- he's on leave.
我记得他说自己是这里最年轻的副队
I remember he said he was the youngest guy here to ever make lieutenant.
一定有几把刷子
Must have made a few waves.
这地方就像狗拉雪橇
Nah. This place is run like a dogsled --
没人突出  只有咕哝
No stars. Just grunts.
一只狗疲了
One mutt goes lame,
另一只跳起来  奋力前进
another one pops up and slogs through the slush.
少陪了
Agent.
我们要见的这个法师
So this, uh, warlock we're meeting --
他是线人吗
He's -- he's a snitch?
警察到处都有线人
Cops have snitches all over town.
詹姆斯怀疑群落里的人  就找德利西尔
James uses Drexyl when he suspects someone in the community.
我得问问
I got to ask.
忍不住想知道
I-I can't help but wonder --
狗和女孩  哪个为先
Which came first, dog or girl?
对
Yeah.
我是说  我只是好奇
Yeah, I mean, I'm just curious
你认为自己主要是哪一个
as to which one you consider yourself, mostly.
这跟我昨晚说的
This have anything to do
我和詹姆斯的事有什么关系吗
with what I told you about James and me last night?
你在想象那幅画面吗
How you're imagining it?
什么
What?
不  那是...
No, that's...
没错
Yes.
德利西尔  这位是迪恩
Drexyl, this is Dean.
底特律的巫士  有耳闻
Wiccan, Detroit. I heard.
情况是这样的
So, here's the deal --
市井上没有巫师诅咒其他巫师的传闻
absolutely no word on the street about any witch hexing another one.
你确定没有这种咒语吗
You sure there's not any kind of spell?
听着  底特律佬  我以消息可靠为傲
Look, Detroit, I pride myself on reliable sourcing.
但关于詹姆斯的流言很多
There is, however, a lot of chatter about our James.
什么样的流言
What kind of chatter?
他已经变成开膛手了
That he's gone ripper.
就像开膛手杰克
As in Jack the...
有人传言称他变成了一个杀手
Someone's circulating the rumor that he's set at full kill.
有人  我们的人吗
"Someone"? One of us?
如果警察听到风声  逮捕詹姆斯
If the cops get wind of it, arrest James,
查出他的真实身份  我们就都暴露了
find out what he really is, that exposes the rest of us.
你知道这绝对不行
You know that can't happen.
意思是
Meaning?
他们会给詹姆斯两个选择
They're gonna give James two choices...
离开或者切腹自杀
Leave or the full hara-kiri.
自杀
Suicide?
巫师们赞赏这份高姿态
Witches appreciate a grand gesture.
我不会让他那么做的
I won't let him do that.
那群落或许会代劳
Well, the community might do it for him.
我一直在查看鲍比的资料
So, I have been going over Bobby's data.
有什么发现吗
Anything?
波西亚也许说的没错
Uh, Portia might not be wrong.
还真有一个咒语
Turns out there is a spell for, uh...
可以把幻像植入另一个人的大脑中
for implanting images into another person's brain.
-真的吗  -是的
- Really? - Yeah.
将虚假的记忆植入另一个巫师脑中
"Creating false memories into another witch's mind."
那詹姆斯可能在完全无罪的情况下
So James could be convinced he killed those other people
被灌输了杀人的想法
without ever touching them.
那凶手或许真的另有其人
So, then, maybe it is somebody else.
是啊  而且还费尽心机陷害詹姆斯
Yeah, who's going to a hell of a lot of trouble to make it look like James.
警方那边怎么说
What'd the cops say?
是这样的
Here's the thing.
艾德・斯托尔兹说他们什么都没找到
Um, according to Ed Stoltz, they got zip,
但他们肯定有发现
But they got something.
我看见在调查此案的技术员
I saw the, uh, tech guy who's working the case,
拿着厚厚的标着"詹姆斯・弗兰普顿"的文件夹
and he had a huge file folder marked "James Frampton".
这艾德没说啊
Ed didn't mention that.
没有
No, he did not.
好吧
All right.
顺便说一句  你值得表扬
Oh, by the way, got to hand it to you.
从波西亚说和詹姆斯那晚的事
It's been 15 hours since Portia
到现在15小时了
mentioned her night with James,
你还没有讲过一则人兽乱交的笑话
and not one bestiality joke out of you.
波西亚告诉我  我群落里的朋友
Portia tells me my friends in the community
想烧死我
wants me burned at the stake.
我不想说谎  事情越来越糟了
I'm not gonna lie. It's, uh...it's getting ugly.
警方对查到的东西可能有所隐瞒
Yeah, the cops may have more on the case than they're saying,
包括一厚本关于你的档案
including a thick dossier on you.
-关于我  -是的
- Me? - Yeah.
我感觉他们调查到的东西
I get the feeling whatever they have
被锁在分局C110房间里
is under lock and key at the precinct, uh, room C-110.
那我们得想办法闯进去
Then we need to break in.
是啊
Sure, yeah.
整天一堆警察的楼里一间上锁的房间
A locked room in a joint crawling with cops 24/7...
我怎么就没想到
Why didn't I think of that?
迪恩  巫师不用亲临也能到一个地方
Dean, a witch can go to a place without having to go to a place.
怎么  像电话性爱
What, like phone sex?
灵魂出窍
Astral projection.
我可以将我的意识投射到任何地方
I can project my awareness anywhere...
就这么躺着就行
From the comfort of right here.
但得解开锁链
But these have got to go.
不可能的事
Not gonna happen.
铐着铁链  就无法施展魔法
Irons on, no magic,
不施展魔法  就闯不进那房间
no magic, no break-in.
那好吧
Okay.
但是我们必须和你一起去
But only if we can go with you.
詹姆斯  你确定你还能做得到吗
James, are you sure you're still even able to do this?
这可真让人信心倍增
Oh, well, that's a confidence builder.
在我灵魂出窍
Anything else I should know
把命交给他之前  还有什么要知道的吗
before I become some disembodied thing, completely at his mercy?
闭上眼睛吧
Just close your eyes.
不管我看到什么  都会传给你们
Whatever I see, I'll pass on to you, too.
[咒语]
Libera me occulta cognoscere veritatem.
东圣路易斯警察局
目击者证词
菲利普・勒沙
詹姆斯  怎么都不给点提示
James, why don't you give us a little warning
就这样把我们拉回来
you're gonna snap us back like that?
斯托尔兹要立案起诉我了
Stoltz -- he's building a case against me.
什么
What?!
艾德  他总想要个大案子
Ed -- he's always wanted a breakthrough case.
抓一个犯事的警察  就够大了
Nailing a renegade cop -- that would qualify.
尤其他对这个警察还怀恨在心
Yeah, especially one he holds a grudge against.
我的第一个案子
My first case
他因此没当上探长
they dropped him as lead detective.
而我当上了
They went with me.
那这算什么  是报复吗
So what is this, you think -- a payback?
他不能逮捕你
He can't just arrest you.
他需要证词  需要证据
He needs evidence. He needs proof.
他已经有了
He's got it!
他什么都有了
He's got everything.
谁的证词
From who?
菲尔  那只猫
Phil. The cat.
菲利普
Philippe.
放轻松
Hey, hey, hey. Take it easy.
詹姆斯  好好说  伙计
James, hey. Talk this out, buddy.
詹姆斯  别  我们一起解决
James, don't! We'll do this together.
不  对你来说太危险了
No, we won't. It's not safe for you.
我们在一起的日子结束了
Our time together is over.
陪伴你是我的责任  我的选择
Standing by you is my duty, my choice!
波西亚  我的天塌了
Portia, the ceiling is coming down on me.
你还有生路
You still have a life.
求你了
Please.
波西亚  走吧
Portia, go.
詹姆斯
James
走
Go!
你不觉得我戴牙套太晚了吗
So, you don't think it's too late for me to wear braces?
你都不会感觉到的
Won't even notice them.
我们会用隐形的
We'll put in transparent.
詹姆斯  你干什么
James, what are you doing?
你为什么要撒谎害我
Why are you telling lies about me?
我没有  我不会的
I'm not. I wouldn't.
我去了证据室
I saw the evidence room.
我看到了警方根据目击证人画的素描像
I saw the police sketch based on an eyewitness account.
滚
Get lost.
求你了  不要
Please, don't.
告诉我为什么
Tell me why.
我别无选择
I had no choice.
什么意思
What does that mean?
我的主人让我这么做的
My master made me.
骗子
Liar.
你是个懦夫和骗子  斯宾塞是我的朋友
You're a coward and a liar. Spencer's my friend.
直接命令
A direct command.
求你了  别伤了我的脸
Please, don't hurt my face.
我没想...
I'm not interested --
他总那么没骨气[脊椎]
He was always spineless.
这下是真的没了
Now literally.
是你
It was you.
你是幕后黑手
You were behind all this?
那我就虚心承认吧
I humbly accept credit.
你让我觉得我是凶手
You made me think I was a killer.
是艾德・斯托尔兹让你这么做的
Ed Stoltz put you up to it.
他发现你是个巫师  想敲诈你
He found out you were a witch, tried to blackmail you.
吉米  你没有动脑思考
You're not using your thinking cap, Jimmy.
实际上  他不相信神秘学这点很关键
It was actually crucial that he didn't believe in the occult.
他的案子铁证如山呢  你说呢
I'd say he's built quite a solid case, don't you?
我不明白
I don't understand.
你当然不明白
Of course you don't.
你们都没有考虑过我的感受
Neither of you ever considered my feelings.
波西亚
Portia?
都是为了她
This is about her?
你能想象她选择了你  对我是多大的侮辱吗
Can you imagine the insult when she chose you?
我第一次见她  就想让她作我的灵魂伴侣
I wanted her as my soul mate the moment I saw her.
她注定是我的灵兽
She was meant to be my familiar.
她可不止是灵兽  不是吗
Oh, she's way more than familiar, isn't she?
她选你做主人  我忍了
When she picked you as master, I endured it.
但你俩开始《暮色》之恋  违反了规矩
But when you two went all Bella and Edward, broke the code,
将你们的激情放在群落规则之前
put your passions before the community rules,
你太自大  权利过剩
Well, the arrogance, the entitlement was too much.
你就应该被摧毁
Your total ruination seemed appropriate.
底特律来的巫士
The wiccan from Detroit.
那詹姆斯没杀死那些...
So James didn't kill those --
你真想跟我较量吗
Seriously, you want to take me on?
快
Hurry.
我不仅仅可以进入詹姆斯的脑袋
It's not only James' head I can get inside.
迪恩
Dean.
萨姆
Sam!
[咒语]
Ego voco impetu delere...
...vos caelum et infernum.
孩子们  切勿在家模仿
Well, kids, don't try this at home.
你真不想留下反击吗
You sure you don't want to stay and fight this?
我们可以帮你
Look, we can help you.
斯宾塞说得对
Eh, Spencer was right.
艾德・斯托尔兹证据确凿
Ed Stoltz has built enough of a case against me
足以折腾我好一阵
to make life hell for a long time,
这里的群落也不想要我们
and the community here wants no part of us.
我们要重新开始
We start over.
习惯了
We're used to it.
总是这样  你们也是如此
So it's always been, for all of us.
我会想你的
I'll miss you.
也许也会想你
Maybe even you.
我喜欢狗
I like dogs.
不  你真的不喜欢
No. You really don't.
我之前可能错了
Well, it's possible I was wrong.
关于詹姆斯吗
What, about James?
伙计  我们都打算去杀他
Dude, we were both ready to gank the guy.
不  我不是说这个
No, that's not what I meant.
之前  斯宾塞控制我们的时候
Back there, when Spencer had us.
他搅乱了我的头脑
He screwed with my head.
我看见了妈妈
I saw mom...
她死的样子
When she died...
还有其他乱七八糟的事情
And then some other crap.
我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
当我回想我们一家所经历的一切
You know, when I look back at what our family's been through,
每个人经历的一切
what everybody's been through,
想到那些痛苦
seeing all that pain...
我意识到  我们能走到现在
I realize that the only way we've made it through it all
全靠彼此相依
is by hanging together.
小萨姆  我信任你
I trust you, Sammy.
这件事
With this deal,
把那些混蛋永远锁在熔炉里
locking those sons of bitches up in the furnace once and for all,
太重要了  我不能不信任你
it's too important not to.
所以如果你说你很好
So if you say you're good...
那么就这样
...then that's it.
我百分之百支持你
I'm with you 100%.
我很好
I'm good.